Guide to the Rice University Bands (MOB) records, 1914-2012 UA 239
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series XXIV: Uniforms, 1921-1990s, 146045
  - Navy-style military hat, n.d. (Box 23)
  - Tall white furry hat, n.d. (Box 23)
  - Tale white furry hat with "R" on it, n.d. (Box 24)
  - Tale white furry hat with "Rice" on it, n.d. (Box 25)
  - Two-piece blue band uniform with silver owl on backside, 1970s (Box 26)
  - White dress shirt with MOB monogram, 1970s (Box 26)
  - Two-piece blue band uniform with vest, 1970s (Box 26)
  - Blue, cream with gold trim bib, n.d. (Box 26)
  - Two-piece gray band uniform, 1940s (Box 27)
  - Two-piece gray band uniform, 1940s (Box 27)
  - "I'm Sending the MOB to Notre Dame" T-shirt, 1988-1989 (Box 27)
  - Three-piece MOB suit, 1980s-2000s (Box 28)
  - Fedora, 1980s-2000s (Box 28)
  - Rice Band belt & buckle: black leather belt with attached buckle reading "Rice Band" in enamel lettering (Box 28)
  - Owl band hat, ca. 1921 (Box 28)
  - Department of Athletics band pass (Box 28)
  - Band medal (Box 28)
  - 2 band sweaters - Harvin C. Moore, 1927 (Box 29)
  - MOB "Unconventional" t-shirt, n.d. (Box 29)
  - MOB staff t-shirt, 2013-2014 (Box 29)
  - MOB Fedora t-shirt, n.d. (Box 29)
  - MOB "Organized chaos" t-shirt, n.d. (Box 29)
  - MOB 40th anniversary t-shirt, 2012 (Box 29)
  - MOB C-USA t-shirt, 2013 (Box 29)
  - MOB bright blue t-shirt, n.d. (Box 29)
  - MOB navy blue t-shirt, n.d. (Box 29)
  - MOB white t-shirt, n.d. (Box 29)
  - MOB Tulsa vs. Rice t-shirt, 2007-11 (Box 29)